export const CONFIG = {
    questions: [
        {
            amount: '$500',
            question: "Which of these philosophers wrote music to Pushkin's poems \"Spell\" and \"Winter Evening\" in 1864?",
            answers: [
                {
                    id: "jung",
                    label: "Jung",
                    letter: "A"
                },
                {
                    id: "hegel",
                    label: "Hegel",
                    letter: "B"
                },
                {
                    id: "nietzsche",
                    label: "Nietzsche",
                    letter: "C"
                },
                {
                    id: "schopenhauer",
                    label: "Schopenhauer",
                    letter: "D"
                }
            ],
            correctAnswer: "nietzsche"
        },
        {
            amount: '$1,000',
            question: "How many times a day do the chimes of the Spasskaya Tower of the Kremlin get wound up?",
            answers: [
                {
                    id: "1",
                    label: "1",
                    letter: "A"
                },
                {
                    id: "2",
                    label: "2",
                    letter: "B"
                },
                {
                    id: "3",
                    label: "3",
                    letter: "C"
                },
                {
                    id: "4",
                    label: "4",
                    letter: "D"
                }
            ],
            correctAnswer: "2"
        },
        {
            amount: '$2,000',
            question: "Who was the first person to win the Nobel Prize for Literature?",
            answers: [
                {
                    id: "romanist",
                    label: "Romanist",
                    letter: "A"
                },
                {
                    id: "playwright",
                    label: "Playwright",
                    letter: "B"
                },
                {
                    id: "poet",
                    label: "Poet",
                    letter: "C",
                },
                {
                    id: "essayist",
                    label: "Essayist",
                    letter: "D"
                }
            ],
            correctAnswer: "poet"
        },
        {
            amount: '$4,000',
            question: "With which letter do the words published in the 16th volume of the latest edition of the Great Soviet Encyclopedia begin?",
            answers: [
                {
                    id: "m",
                    label: "M",
                    letter: "A"
                },
                {
                    id: "n",
                    label: "N",
                    letter: "B"
                },
                {
                    id: "o",
                    label: "O",
                    letter: "C"
                },
                {
                    id: "p",
                    label: "P",
                    letter: "D"
                }
            ],
            correctAnswer: "o"
        },
        {
            amount: '$8,000',
            question: "Which of the following was a page at the time of Catherine II?",
            answers: [
                {
                    id: "fonvisin",
                    label: "D.I. Fonvisin",
                    letter: "A"
                },
                {
                    id: "derzhavin",
                    label: "G.R. Derzhavin",
                    letter: "B"
                },
                {
                    id: "radishchev",
                    label: "A.N. Radishchev",
                    letter: "C"
                },
                {
                    id: "karamzin",
                    label: "N.M. Karamzin",
                    letter: "D"
                }
            ],
            correctAnswer: "radishchev"
        },
        {
            amount: '$16,000',
            question: "What chemical element is named after the evil underground dwarf?",
            answers: [
                {
                    id: "hafnium",
                    label: "Hafnium",
                    letter: "A"
                },
                {
                    id: "cobalt",
                    label: "Cobalt",
                    letter: "B"
                },
                {
                    id: "beryllium",
                    label: "Beryllium",
                    letter: "C"
                },
                {
                    id: "tellurium",
                    label: "Tellurium",
                    letter: "D"
                }
            ],
            correctAnswer: "cobalt"
        },
        {
            amount: '$32,000',
            question: "In which of these capitals of the former Soviet republics did the subway appear first?",
            answers: [
                {
                    id: "tbilisi",
                    label: "Tbilisi",
                    letter: "A"
                },
                {
                    id: "yerevan",
                    label: "Yerevan",
                    letter: "B"
                },
                {
                    id: "baku",
                    label: "Baku",
                    letter: "C"
                },
                {
                    id: "minsk",
                    label: "Minsk",
                    letter: "D"
                }
            ],
            correctAnswer: "tbilisi"
        },
        {
            amount: '$64,000',
            question: "How many seas surround the Balkan Peninsula?",
            answers: [
                {
                    id: "3",
                    label: "3",
                    letter: "A"
                },
                {
                    id: "4",
                    label: "4",
                    letter: "B"
                },
                {
                    id: "5",
                    label: "5",
                    letter: "C"
                },
                {
                    id: "6",
                    label: "6",
                    letter: "D"
                }
            ],
            correctAnswer: "6"
        },
        {
            amount: '$125,000',
            question: "What is the name of the river that does not exist in Russia?",
            answers: [
                {
                    id: "neck",
                    label: "Neck",
                    letter: "A"
                },
                {
                    id: "charter",
                    label: "Charter",
                    letter: "B"
                },
                {
                    id: "back",
                    label: "Back",
                    letter: "C"
                },
                {
                    id: "finger",
                    label: "Finger",
                    letter: "D"
                }
            ],
            correctAnswer: "back"
        },
        {
            amount: '$250,000',
            question: "What is a lobo?",
            answers: [
                {
                    id: "reaper",
                    label: "Reaper",
                    letter: "A"
                },
                {
                    id: "hat",
                    label: "Hat",
                    letter: "B"
                },
                {
                    id: "disease",
                    label: "Disease",
                    letter: "C"
                },
                {
                    id: "furnace",
                    label: "Furnace",
                    letter: "D"
                }
            ],
            correctAnswer: "reaper"
        },
        {
            amount: '$500,000',
            question: "What novel did Fenimore Cooper write on a bet with his wife?",
            answers: [
                {
                    id: "precaution",
                    label: "\"Precaution\"",
                    letter: "A"
                },
                {
                    id: "pioneers",
                    label: "\"Pioneers\"",
                    letter: "B"
                },
                {
                    id: "last of the Mohicans",
                    label: "\"Last of the Mohicans\"",
                    letter: "C"
                },
                {
                    id: "st. John's Wort",
                    label: "\"St. John's Wort.\"",
                    letter: "D"
                }
            ],
            correctAnswer: "precaution"
        },
        {
            amount: '$1,000,000',
            question: "What name has not been adopted by any pope?",
            answers: [
                {
                    id: "valentin",
                    label: "Valentin",
                    letter: "A"
                },
                {
                    id: "eugene",
                    label: "Eugene",
                    letter: "B"
                },
                {
                    id: "george",
                    label: "George",
                    letter: "C"
                },
                {
                    id: "victor",
                    label: "Victor",
                    letter: "D"
                }
            ],
            correctAnswer: "george"
        },
    ]
}